A Guide to the John Wells research notes, 1871-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Architect lists and card files, n.d., Extent: 18 boxes. (Box 1-15c)
  - Brown, A. Ten Eyck (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Brown, Thomas S. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Brown, W.K. & Brothers (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Bruce, A.C. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Buddemeyer, Edwin (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Bull, Louis H. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Bunting & Rosenplaenter (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Burford, F.H.P. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Burke, C.C. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Burke & McConnell (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Burkhalter, Hickerson & Associates (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Burklatter, Hickerson & Associates (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Burnett, George W. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Burnette, Berneice (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Burhham, Herbert M. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Burts, Joseph S. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Cairns, Bayard (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Cairns, Bayard S. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Carlton, Charles W. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Carpenter & Blair (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Carter, James (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Carter, Morton & Associates (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Chamberlin, W. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Chamberlin, _ (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Chandler, Albert G. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Chighizola, August A. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Churchill, W.D. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Clark, Edward M. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Clark, Horace W. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Clark, John Howard (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Clarke, Eli & John Wesley(Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Clausel, Floyd E. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Colley, Clarence K. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Cole, Thomas L. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Community Techtonics, Inc. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Cook, James B. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Cook, James Bartholomew (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - Copeland, Joe (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Covington, Albert M. (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Cowardin, Major (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - Cox & Walton (Tennessee) (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Crutchfield, Thomas, Sr. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Curtin, _ (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Damron, John (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Danforth, Josiah (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Davis, Thomas J. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Deacon, Richard G. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - DeKalb, Walt M. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Dent, Lucian Minor (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Dickey, D. Anderson (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dodd, _ (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Dolan, T.J. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Donner, _ (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Doriot, Henri (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Dougherty, Edward Emmet (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Dow, D.L. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Dryden, Allen N. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Dunkerly, Victor (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Duvall, C. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Eason, W. Jeter (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Eely, Fred H. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Ehrman, M.G. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Ellis, Charles W., Jr. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Engestfeldt, Louis (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Faulk, J. Hays (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Ferguson, Charles A. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Fleming, William M. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Frahn, Harry J.(Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Franklin, Selmon T. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Fuller, James (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Furbringer, Max (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Gaddis, John W. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Gaisford, John (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Gailoway & Guthrie (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Gamble, Robert (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Gardner, Thomas West (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Garrett, S.L.P. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Gaut, R.E (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Gholson, Benjamin (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Gildard, William H. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Gillispie, Paul (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Goodloe & Nicholson (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Graf, Herbert Raymond (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Graf, Richard Franklin (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Graf, _ (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Gredig, Albert E. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Guenther, Grederick B. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Hain, Henderson J. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Hake, Harry (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Hammond, Horace B. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Hanker, William J. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Harris, Jack Shields (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Harris, William C., Jr. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Hart, _ (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Hart, Freeland & Roberts (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Hastings, _ (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Hawkins, Hermon (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Heavner, Uriah R. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Heiman, Adolphus (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Henderson, M.E. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Hickman Brothers (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Hirons, Frederick C. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Hise, Frank (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Holland & Williams (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Holmes, _ (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Hoover, Henry (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Houston, John (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Howard, Nielson, Lyne, Batey & O'Brien (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Hulsey, Howel B. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Hunt, Reuben H. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Hunt & Lamm (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Hust, William (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Hutchings, _ (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Irvine, Josephus (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Jones, C.T. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Johnson, Cyrus F. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Jones, Dudley (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Jones, Edward Culliatt (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Jones, John (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Kahn, Albert (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Kaucher, Hodges & Company (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Kearfott, Clarence B. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Keeley, Patrick (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Kenfott, Bo (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Kerr, William (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Kiker, _ (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Kirby, Marion A. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Kramer, Henry J. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Krider, C.V. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Lester, William C. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - LeVasseur & Company (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Lide, Martin J. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Lindsey, Claude H. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Loggans, C.W. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Lowe, Thomas (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Lyle, John (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Mack, Clyde E. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Maffett, Howard & Associates (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Mahan, George, Jr. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Manley, Fred J. (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Manley, Young & Meyer (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Marr, Thomas Scott (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Martin, Ann (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Martin, Harry (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Mathas, John (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - McBryde, James (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - McCorkle, Samuel (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - McDonald Brothers (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - McElroy Brothers (Tennessee) (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - McGee, Hubert T. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - McGeoy Frank R. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - McGown, Daniel T. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - McKinnon, Daniel (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - McKissack, James T. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - McMurray, Benjamin F. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Melick, Neal A. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Meridith, Elish (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Michael, H.H. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Miller, John W. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell, C.G. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Mitchell, James C. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Moore, John (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Morton-Carter & Associates (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Moyers, Allbright & Turley (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Murry, Phillip (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Myer, Clem (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Mytton, Rich G.V. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Nader, John (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Neville, L.J. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Norton, George C. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Owen, W.C. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Parmelee, M.E. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Parmelee, _ (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Patton, Joe B. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Patton, R.B. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Patton, William (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Pauley, J.P. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Penn, Thomas H. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Pfeil, Charles O. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Porter, James (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Price, Mike (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Regan, R.J. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Richardson, R.B. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Rickman, _ (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Ritter, H.W. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Roberts, Collin H. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Rogers, James Gamble (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Ross, Charles C. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Ryno, John H. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Scarborough, John (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Shappley, Arnold, Jr. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Shepherd, Percy B. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Smith & Banks (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Smith, Benjamin N. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Smith & Pevahouse (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Smith, G. Tandy, Jr. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Smith, William C. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Speight & Hibbs (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Stanfill, Charles T. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Stanford & Harr (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Steinbaugh & Wheeler (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Stephenson & Getaz (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Strickland, W.F. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Strickland, William (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Sweeney, Calvin (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Swern, Perry (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Tate, L.E. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Taylor, H.P. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Thomas, E.R. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Thomas, Nathan (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Thomas, William A. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Thompson, Charles L. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Tisdale, Pinson & Stone (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Turbeville, Robert E. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Taylor, Jacke H. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Vanderbrook, Peter L. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Vannay, G.B. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Von Nerta, George O. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Wage, William M. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Walden, Charles G. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Wallace, Joe T. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Warren, R.Q. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Waters, L.C. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Watkins, William (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Weathers, Lundie Monroe (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Whittice, Robert D. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Williams, G. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Williams, John R.D. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Williams, Mike (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Willis, Sloan & Trigg (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Wilson & Odom (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Wood, William Halsey (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Woolwine, Emmons S. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Yeaman, James H. (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Yearwood, Nile (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Yearwood & Johnson (Tennessee) (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Anderson, D. Wiley (Virginia) (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Bailey, I. Lincoln (Virginia) (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Bailey, J. Russell (Virginia) (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Baskervill, _ (Virginia) (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Barber, George Franklin (Virginia) (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Baylor, J.A. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Beauchamp, H. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Blackburn, Thomas R. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Bruce & Morgan (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Bryant, Charles K. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Budd, Katherine Cotheal (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Cain, Herbert Levi (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Clinton & Russell (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Coit, Elisabeth (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Colavita, Philip, Jr. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cluss, Adolf (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Cutler, Howard (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Cutshaw, Wilfred E. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Dozier, Henrietta Cuttino (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Deitrick, W.H. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Dwyer, H. Irving (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Edwards, William Augustus (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Ficklin, George (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Flagg, Ernest (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Fleming, William Henry Irwin (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Foulk, S.W. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Gassaway, Minnie Quinn (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Ghequier, T. Buckler (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Hair, Nell Roper (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Hammarskold, P.H. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Harvey, C.K. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Hayes, E. Paul (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Heard, G. Bryant (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Hentz, Reid & Adler (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Howell, Claude K. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Huggines, Harrie (Henry) Hartwell (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Hunt, Reuben Harrison (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Johnson, Harvey N. (Virginia) (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Johnson & Brannan (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Jones, Clarence T. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Jones & Furbringer (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Kellogg, Fay (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - LaFarge, Louis Bancel (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lafever, Minard (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Lankford, John A. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Lee, Duncan (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Lee, William Edward, Jr. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Legnaioli, Ferrucio (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, John Minor Botts (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Lind, Edmund G. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Lockwood, Greene & Company (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Loewy, Raymond (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Lybrock, Albert (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Magruder, Evalina (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Makielski, Stanislaw J. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Mann, Estes W. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Milburn, Frank Pierce (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Owen, John D., Jr. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Percival, William (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Read, Charles H., Jr. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Robinson, Charles M. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Saul, Warren A. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Saville, Allen J. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Sayre, C. Gadsden (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Shattuck & Hussey (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Simon, Louis A. (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Sloan, John (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Snyder, Jacob (Virginia) (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Starkweather, Norris G. (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Stoddart, William L. (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Taylor, James Knox (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Thomas, John R. (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Tinsley, Walter P. (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Tompkins, D.A. (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Turner, Joseph Clifford (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Veal, Thomas (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Welmer, Kenneth F. (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Wenderoth, Oscar (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - West, Albert L. (Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Adair, R.H. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Connell, George E. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Faris, F.F. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Franzheim, Edward B. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Giesey, M.F. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Gladden, A.P. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Hickman, Charles L. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Holmboe, E.C. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Holmes, Julius C. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Jacobs, Elmer F. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Lafferty, Robert E. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Leiner, Joseph (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Lyons, A.C. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - McCarty, Charles D. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Patton, William Howe (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Rohr, M.J. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Sanderson, Edward T. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Stewart, J.B. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Tibbetts, John C. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Wiggins, P.N. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Wood, E.J. (West Virginia) (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Notecards (Box 15a)
  - Notecards (Box 15b)
  - Notecards (Box 15c)
- Series II. Manufactuer's Record, 1890-1948., Extent: 32 boxes. (Box 16-47)
  Series II. Includes clippings taken from the self-titled serial, which documented the development of manufacturing and industry in the South in the early to mid-twentieth century.
  The majority of this series is arranged alphabetically by state. Boxes 16-20 are arranged chronologically.
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1890 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1891 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1892 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1893 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1894 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1895 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1896 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1897 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1898 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1899 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1900 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1901 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1902 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1906 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1906 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1908 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1908 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1909 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1909 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1910 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1913 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1918 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Manufacturer's Record, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Alabama, 1897 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Alabama, 1898 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Alabama, 1899 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Alabama, 1900 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Alabama, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Alabama, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Alabama, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Alabama, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Alabama, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Alabama, 1920 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Alabama, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Alabama, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Alabama, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Alabama, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Alabama, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Alabama, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Arkansas, 1892 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Arkansas, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Arkansas, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Arkansas, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Arkansas, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Florida, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Florida, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Florida, 1897 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Florida, 1898 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Florida, 1899 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Florida, 1900 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Florida, 1901 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Florida, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Florida, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Florida, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Florida, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Florida, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Florida, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Florida, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Florida, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Florida, 1931 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Florida, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Georgia, 1892 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Georgia, 1893 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Georgia, 1894 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Georgia, 1895 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Georgia, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Georgia, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Georgia, 1898 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Georgia, 1899 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Georgia, 1900 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Georgia, 1901 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Georgia, 1902 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Georgia, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Georgia, 1907 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Georgia, 1909 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Georgia, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Georgia, 1911 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Georgia, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Georgia, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Georgia, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Georgia, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Georgia, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Georgia, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Georgia, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Georgia, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Georgia, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Georgia, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Georgia, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Georgia, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Georgia, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Georgia, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Georgia, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Georgia, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Georgia, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Georgia, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Georgia, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Georgia, 1931 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Georgia, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Kentucky, 1897 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Kentucky, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Kentucky, 1917 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Kentucky, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Kentucky, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Kentucky, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Kentucky, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Kentucky, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Kentucky, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Kentucky, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Louisiana, 1897 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Louisiana, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Louisiana, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Louisiana, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Louisiana, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Louisiana, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Louisiana, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Louisiana, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Louisiana, 1931 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Louisiana, 1932 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Maryland, 1916 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Maryland, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 4)